[Applause]
wow what a beautiful day you know the
forecast right here in front of me says
it's continued fair weather through
tomorrow skies are gonna be clear and
there's gonna be a hobby of a tail
beside the golf ball size of baseball i
think we better move this party indoors
all right that's fine all right
all right somebody get the food
don't panic
[Music]
i'll call prudential why complain to
them about the weather life insurance
won't repair your home not life
homeowners we have a piece of the rock
for our home too
your prudential agent can be more than
your friend for life the same agent can
help protect your home and car too and
four out of five claims like these are
handled by phone i'm covered
thanks prudential you can plan on plenty
of sunshine today so get to the great
outdoors life health auto home
prudential insurance